[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What are you looking at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Not yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Am I about to die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Here's the reason, as a friend, that I want to highlight this last number for you, which is your blood pressure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Dr. Oz, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Very, very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What is the best advice for people to get to January and think New Year, new me, new start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, resolutions actually do make a difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What are the things about the American diet, the way of life, whatever it may be, that are particular, perhaps, to America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, we have made it easy to do the wrong thing in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Just from French fries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Just from French fries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "RBR", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "If everybody just exercised better portion control, literally cut the amount they ate by, say, a third, what effect would that have on the average life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "It would dramatically change our life expectancy, but, more importantly, the quality of our life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Is it good for America that you have a first lady and president who are obviously very physically fit themselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It's a huge benefit for the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "If you walked as an adult for half an hour a day -- you know, I walk here across Central Park, say, to CNN, and I feel like it's a pretty good exercise if you walk at a reasonable pace, is that enough to be fit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "It's a perfect amount.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "LOCATION": ["Central Park"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Why do you think you've had a battle with your weight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "If I could figure it out, I'd fix it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "You don't know what it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Did you ever get help for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Sure, plenty of times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Where do you -- where do you fall down in terms of dealing with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "I eat too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Should they have the jab?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I think they should have the flu shot, without question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What is the best advice, if there is any, for people who get caught up in these terrible tragedies, about how to somehow get back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "What we ought, I think, crave is hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "How do you deal with that particular kind of stress, a really -- like a death in the family, a death of a close friend, even, for some people, a death of a beloved pet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Piers, I can't tell you how many times we've lost one couple, a long married couple, and then soon after, we'll lose the spouse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Is that -- does it exist in medical terms, a broken heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "There is no question at all that broken hearts exist and they kill people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Rhodiola?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Rhodiola is Siberian ginseng.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Are you basically telling me you've been half cut on vodka your entire career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Can we add a few, you know, cannabis joints to the equation now that they're legal in some states?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Cannabis, a fascinating story, in part because there is no question there's medicinal benefit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "How addictive is cannabis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "It's addictive as cigarettes, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Is it more dangerous than cigarettes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "It -- it has more dangers in part because when you're under the influence of cannabis, your judgment is a bit more affected than it would be under cigarettes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "But if you, as one of America's topmost renowned doctors, says it's not more dangerous than cigarettes, surely, it should just be legalized, then, right, like cigarettes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "There are a couple of problems with cannabis.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "But how bad is that, with the mass index?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, the body mass index is -- it's in the overweight category, but I'm not that worried about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "So you're 6'1\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "''", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Six-one, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What should my waist be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Half of your height, half of 73 inches, which is 36 and a half inches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "How bad is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, ideally it would be less than 140.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What's mine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Thirty-seven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "I need more healthy -- how do I get more healthy cholesterol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "The best way to do it is to get that waist size down to 36 and a half inches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What's the best way to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "There are a couple of little tips.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "But can I share that for a second?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ":", "RB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "How high?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "It's supposed to be -- ideally about 115 over 75, ideally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "And what causes that kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Exercise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "So what should I be doing to deal with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Well, the number one thing that folks ought to start doing is to automate their lives so the easy decisions are the right ones and are easier to make.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Is that bad for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Coffee itself is fine, because it's -- it's the number one source of antioxidants in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "-- I'm going to get you back in -- how long would I need to try and really deal with this?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "You could dramatically change these numbers in six weeks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Or is it just luck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Well, it's a combination.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "So my question to you is, is there a preventative measure that I could use to help alleviate the pain so that, long-term, it won't turn into arthritis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "That's a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "What is the best way to try and deal with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "You know, we tackle this on the show a lot because there's actually 116 million Americans with chronic pain issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "And what's the balance between genetics and just good living?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "It turns out that about two thirds of how long you live is based on your lifestyle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "What is the secret to long life, do you think, in terms of health?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Good diet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "Do what in bed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Let me ask you, have you ever smoked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Milk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "What about that for a recipe for long life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "It's obviously worked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 811, "question": "And if you can't get enough, what do you do about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 812, "answer": "The number one under appreciated health problem in America is sleep issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "It can't help you sleep, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "It completely disrupts sleep patterns, and for one very important reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "You cannot get the flu from the flu shot because the material is actually dead flu virus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "You're enjoying this, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "This is literally the biggest needle I could find.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 895, "question": "Should children have them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 896, "answer": "It's recommended that after the age of six months, that we give it to our kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 919, "question": "How much of it is mental in the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 920, "answer": "You know, mental is where you win it all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]